<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Kingdoms>

  <Kingdom id="volhynia"
		   owner="Hero.lord_volyan_1a"
		   banner_key="11.83.48.1836.1836.767.764.1.0.0.510.11.40.250.220.955.795.0.0.90.510.11.40.250.220.573.795.0.0.90.510.11.40.470.220.764.909.0.0.0.510.11.40.405.220.765.667.0.0.90.510.11.40.220.220.765.570.0.0.0.510.11.40.150.220.765.697.0.0.0.512.11.40.240.163.764.839.0.0.0.512.83.40.95.65.764.839.0.0.0.510.11.40.60.220.692.838.0.0.0.510.11.40.60.220.836.838.0.0.0.510.11.40.230.220.913.764.0.1.51.510.11.40.230.220.614.764.0.0.308.510.83.40.120.220.585.681.0.0.308.510.83.40.120.220.943.681.0.1.51.510.83.40.120.220.984.689.0.1.90.510.83.40.120.220.544.689.0.1.90.510.11.40.120.220.739.953.0.0.308.510.11.40.120.220.789.953.0.1.51.504.11.40.80.72.764.985.0.1.180"
		   primary_banner_color="0xffd22e31"
		   secondary_banner_color="0xffefc990"
		   label_color="ffd22e31"
		   color="ffd22e31"
		   color2="ffefc990"
		   alternative_color="ffd22e83"
		   alternative_color2="ffefc990"
		   culture="Culture.volhynian"
		   settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_a"
		   flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_a"
		   name="{=volhynia_kingdom_name}The Volhynia Principality"
		   short_name="{=volhynia_kingdom_short_name}Volhynia"
		   title="{=volhynia_kingdom_title}Volhynia Principality"
		   ruler_title="{=volhynia_ruler_title}Knyaz"
		   text="{=volhynia_kingdom_text}The idea that Rus was a monolithic state with a single ethnos, formed by the later Empires, which wanted to create an illusion of unity of its population. In reality, Rus has never controlled the territory drawn on the maps. The territory was home to many ethnic groups and principalities that fought, traded, and befriended each other. The main unifying factor was Christianity, but it was practiced by a minority who were the elite. The main population was pagan. Over time, the elite spread the culture to the general population, but this happened many centuries after the collapse of Rus. In 1097 to stop the endless wars was organized Liubech Congress, at which the separate branches of the once united dynasty divided the power. Possession of the Volhynian Principality was legally given to Davyd Igorovich. In the same year 1097, with the support of the Kyivan Grand Knyaz, Davyd Igorovich started a war with the Terebovlian prince, whom he blinded. Toward the end of his life, as a result of diplomatic and military games, Davyd Igorovich lost the title of Volhynian Prince, but had extensive holdings.">
    <relationships>
		<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.halych" value="-30" isAtWar="true" />
		<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.kyiv" value="-30" isAtWar="true" />
	</relationships>
    <policies>

	</policies>
  </Kingdom>
  
 </Kingdoms>